[Music]
Hello and welcome. My name is Monica Aja
and we'll be talking about enhancement
that we have made for Copilot summaries
in this wave. Copilot is your AI
assistant for work and it has an ability
now to summarize any record on business
central by clearly figuring out what's
important and urgent for you. Copilot
here uses AI to make you understand what
matters most in unrecord and helps you
save effort and time by saving the
navigation that you would need to do
across multiple screens uh and thereby
helps making decision faster and what's
best about this that it is seamlessly
integrated in business central and it is
ready to use. So which means you don't
need to export data. You don't need to
think about what to start writing to
copilot or what to prompt. It's just
readily available and you can get your
insights at a glance.
Let me show you how it works and the
enhancements that we have made in this
release.
Let's start with navigating to a
customer card. Here we are on a customer
card and in the last release we
introduced a new space dedicated for
co-pilot to provide clear and concise
summary based on the role. In this case
copilot summary is producing three
bullet points and as you would have
noticed one of the new enhancements that
we have done is that the summary
generation process is 50% faster. My
role currently is of accountant and
summary is telling me the main important
things that I need to know as an
accountant. For example, the balance due
and overdue payments, the last payment
received amount and date and the ongoing
activities. For popular pages like
customer card, we have done another
enhancements like introducing some new
fields. So we that can be used by
copilot so that we can have even
enriched insights
and as you can see the summary is
actually interactive. So we can go and
click on the field or click on the
interaction and then you will see how it
highlights on a given field. It will
also open the related pages from which
it took the insights for.
And if you just want more insights then
you can click on show more. Then what
will happen here is that it will
actually generate
uh not only the current insights that
you have seen in the fatbox but give you
list of more insights and here you can
use this pane to communicate further
with the co-pilot. For example, in this
case it's telling the total outstanding
invoice value and the current customer
balance and how many activities are
there. You can also further reflect how
can I set uh credit limit for example.
and you can continue the conversation
with the co-pilot.
The new enhancements also include a
capability to actually copy your summary
and share with co-workers and you can do
so by either using the option that we
have from the fact box or pressing Ctrl
C
and then you can just uh use teams or
any other medium that you want. In this
case, it will provide a formatted
summary that is easily sharable with
your co-workers.
Let's try another entity for example,
chart of accounts.
Here I am on the chart of accounts list.
And let's take an example account for
example customers domestic. And you can
see that the balance here is around
44,000.
What I would like to do is now add a
filter by customer group that has only
large business. And you can see now the
balance has changed from 44,000 to
32,000. Let's now navigate into this
card. So here you can see that the
summary is also taking into consider the
filters that were propagated from list
to cart. This is also another
enhancement that we have made in this
release. Summarize with copilot has been
available in all regions and in all
localizations and it is also available
in all languages but only English was
supported until this release and now we
support 20 more languages. As you can
see here an example of summarization
working with Danish language. Also,
summarization works with custom pages.
Although the developers do not have an
access of directly influencing the
summary, but developers can choose to
impact how the summaries could work
based on these custom fields and pages.
And now from this release onwards, we
are also introducing and developer way
for configuring whether they want the
summarization
uh on a certain page uh using AL.
So here's the list of all the
enhancements uh that we have done for
copilot summarization including the
support for more than 20 languages, the
faster generation, the ability to share
the filter awareness, richer insights
and more developer configuration. So if
you want to go ahead and try it out, it
is already available for all business
central online countries and regions.
And it's also available for all type of
environments in all languages. Now it's
with support of 20 languages and it
works with all all card and document
pages. Thank you for watching and if you
like it, please like and subscribe to
our channel. Thank you.